Register of the Richard V. Allen papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs, 1968-1999 (Box-folder 99-104)
  - Northrup-Grumman, 2 prints, 1983 (Box-folder 100: 30)
  - Unidentified party, 19 prints, 1983 (Box-folder 100: 31)
  - German American tricentennial, 5 prints, 1983 (Box-folder 100: 32)
  - Allen with others, 10 prints, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 100: 33)
  - Meeting in Madrid, 1 print, 1984 (Box-folder 100: 34)
  - NASA images, 9 prints, 1984 February 15 (Box-folder 100: 35)
  - Unidentified negatives, 23 negatives, 1984 May (Box-folder 101: 1)
  - Roh Tae Woo visit, 31 prints, 1984 (Box-folder 101: 2-3)
  - Seoul, Korea, 1986 October (Box-folder 101: 4)
  - Allen receiving award, 13 prints, circa 1986 (Box-folder 101: 5)
  - Chung Ju Jung visit, 10 prints, 1986 May (Box-folder 101: 6)
  - Allen and C.S. Low, 3 prints, 1986 November 19 (Box-folder 101: 7)
  - Allen with others, 3 prints, 1986, 1990 (Box-folder 101: 8)
  - Award ceremony at Plaza Hotel, 32 prints, circa 1986 (Box-folder 101: 9-10)
  - Poolside photographs, 5 prints, 1987 June (Box-folder 101: 11)
  - Allen with General Wen Ha-Hsiung in Seoul, 2 prints, 1987 (Box-folder 101: 12)
  - Visit with Congressman David Pong, 8 prints, 1987 Spring (Box-folder 101: 13)
  - Seoul Olympics, 10 prints, 1988 (Box-folder 101: 14)
  - Republican National Convention, 2 prints, 1988 (Box-folder 101: 15)
  - Allen with others in Taiwan, 6 prints, 1988 (Box-folder 101: 16)
  - Photo Album for Dr. Richard V. Allen, American Heritage Foundation, Attending the State Funeral of the Late President Chiang Ching-Kuo of the Republic of China, 1988 January 30 (Box-folder 103)
  - Danny Thompson Memorial Golf Tournament, 7 prints, 1989 July (Box-folder 101: 17)
  - Allen and unidentified woman, 2 prints, 1989 September. (Box-folder 101: 18)
    Official photographs from the Japanese Prime Minister's Office
  - Meeting with C. J. Chen and General Hau, 3 prints, 1990 (Box-folder 101: 19)
  - Kuwait, 80 negatives and 85 prints, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 101: 20-26)
  - Matted and inscribed photograph of Y. S. Sun, 1991 (Box-folder 104)
  - Freedom flight, 1 album, 1991 March 13-16 (Box-folder 104)
  - Paris, 2 prints, 1991 March 6 (Box-folder 101: 27)
  - Richard Allen and Anthony Yeh, 1 print, 1991 September (Box-folder 101: 28)
  - Allen with others in front of the Capitol building, 4 prints, 1991 (Box-folder 101: 29)
  - Taejon exposition and Allen Company office, 1 album, circa 1993 (Box-folder 103)
  - Aichi visit, 5 prints, 1997 July (Box-folder 101: 30)
  - Event at the Van Andel Center, 10 prints, 1997 July 17 (Box-folder 101: 31)
  - Gerhart Niemeyer, Intercollegiate Studies Institute Lifetime Achievement Award, 18 prints and 21 negatives, 1997 (Box-folder 101: 32)
  - Korea and Asia, 8 prints, 1998, undated (Box-folder 101: 33)
  - Allen and Hong Soon Young, 2 prints, 1998 August 20 (Box-folder 101: 34)
- Audiovisual materials, 1948-1999 (Box-folder 105-132)
  Audio cassettes and videotapes documenting Allen's many interviews, speeches, and conferences. Related material can be found in the Speeches and Writings series. Arranged by physical format. The VHS videotapes are further subdivided into groups preserving the original order: News and talk shows, Sporting events, Iran hostage crisis/October surprise, and Miscellaneous.
  - Audiocassettes, 1948-1999 (Box-folder 105-106)
    - Thursday - 5 to 6 pm, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Packwood, 2 copies, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen microcassette, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Howard Squadron, Chairman, Conference of Presidents of Major Jewish Organizations, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - WCLY President's Christmas songs, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - President Habib, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen - American Focus, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Tape of Bonn talk, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - DDU- Mr. Allen, PDU - Tokyo, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen with Boyd France and Lee Kvalczak of Business Week, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen - Interview with Jennifer Byres, Australian National TV, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen - Interview, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen - Interview with Jim Gerstenzang (AP), undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Dvorak's 8 Symphony no. 5, undated (Box-folder 105)
    - Hakone, 1948 May 19 (Box-folder 105)
    - Mario Soare in Bos, 1976 January 24 (Box-folder 105)
    - Japanese Diet Conference, 2 audiocassettes and 2 minicassettes, Taped in Fred Fielding's office, 1979 February 22 (Box-folder 105)
    - Allen, 1980 October 4 (Box-folder 105)
    - Brady Briefing, 1980 December 18 (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen Interview with Mark Hopkins, 1981 April 10 (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen briefing Roosevelt Room, 1981 April 23 (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen Manfred Geist Interview, 1981 May 4 (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen, Newsmaker Sunday, 1981 May 16 (Box-folder 105)
    - CNN interview, 1981 May 16 (Box-folder 105)
    - NYT Interview, 1981 June 23 (Box-folder 105)
    - Herr Bilges, Bild Zeitung, 1981 August 12 (Box-folder 105)
    - The Larry King Show (6 audiocassettes), 1981 December 1-2 (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen - UPI Roundtable, 1981 December 4 (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard Allen, Open Forum, 1981 December 8 (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard Allen, Stanford University Bishop Auditorium, 1982 March 1 (Box-folder 105)
    - Interview with Steve Goldberg, Media News General, 1982 April 12 (Box-folder 105)
    - Kaleidoscope Richard V. Allen, WAMU, 1982 August 4 (Box-folder 105)
    - CBC, 1983 April 23 (Box-folder 105)
    - Albosta/Debategate interview of Richard Allen, CLOSED, 1983 July 6. (Box-folder 105)
    - Richard V. Allen on WRC talking about Reagan trade policy with Soviets, 1983 August 3 (Box-folder 105)
    - WRC Soviet downing of KAL007, 1983 September 1 (Box-folder 106)
    - Face the Nation, 1986 June 1 (Box-folder 106)
    - Richard Allen, American Leadership Conference speech, 1986 December (Box-folder 106)
    - Cutlybert, "Open phones on Reagan countdown," WAMU, 1988 January 20 (Box-folder 106)
    - Lora Cannon, 1989 April 27 (Box-folder 106)
    - Hostages and the 1980 campaign, Monitor Radio, 2 audiocassettes, 1989 November 3 (Box-folder 106)
    - Teure Worte - "Die Ratgeber von Washington, Sender Freies Berlin", 1990 January 28 (Box-folder 106)
    - National Public Radio, Diane Rehm Show, 2 audiocassettes, 1991 May 2 (Box-folder 106)
    - Interview with Ron Ostrow LA Times regarding 1980 Anderson Campaign and October Surprise, 3-May-91 (Box-folder 106)
    - USA Today 10 minute telephone interview, 6-May-91 (Box-folder 106)
    - Richard Allen WX press Vince Foster suicide, NPR, 1993 August 14 (Box-folder 106)
    - Somalia - Dick Allen, CBS Radio with Gil Gross, 1993 October 7 (Box-folder 106)
    - Military Power in the Nineties, Conservative Leadership Conference, 1993 (Box-folder 106)
    - Leading journalists discuss the 1995 State of the Union Address, Sponsored by Lockheed (Box-folder 106)
    - CCA conference cassettes, 17 audiocassettes, 1995 (Box-folder 106)
    - Christian Coalition, "An Agenda for the New Congress,", 1995 January 17 (Box-folder 106)
    - Memorial Service for Donald J. Lipsett, 1995 November 4 (Box-folder 106)
    - NSC/Allen, Newsweek on Air, 1997 March 23 (Box-folder 106)
    - Allen interview, 1997 September 30 (Box-folder 106)
    - Pak-India/Allen, Newsweek On Air, 1998 May 31 (Box-folder 106)
    - Howard Phillips and Hank Cooper, Defense and Foreign Policy, 2 audiocassetes, 1999 January 22-23 (Box-folder 106)
    - Freedom Line with Mike Hambrick, 1999 May 29 (Box-folder 106)
  - Videocassettes, 1980-1999. Format is VHS tape unless otherwise noted (Box-folder 107-135)
    - Video log, 1999 June 29 (Box-folder 107)
    - News and Talk Shows, 1980-1999 (Box-folder 107-116)
      - ABC 1945-1985, undated (Box-folder 107)
      - ABC News Viewpoint, "Media invasion of privacy,", 1982 August 12 (Box-folder 107)
      - ABC Half-time report, 1986 December 15 (Box-folder 107)
      - ABC Peter Jennings, 20/20 Sam Donaldson, 1986 December 15-18 (Box-folder 107)
      - ABC 20/20 Dr. Medenica, and Great Decisions Vietnam and Cambodia, 1990 March 9-10 (Box-folder 107)
      - ABC Good Morning America, 1986 March 27 (Box-folder 107)
      - ABC Good Morning America, 2 cassettes, 1990 January 25 (Box-folder 107)
      - ABC Good Morning America, 1994 June (Box-folder 107)
      - America the Vulnerable, 1998 March (Box-folder 107)
      - America's Voice with Mary Madeleine, 2 cassettes, 1999 June 9 (Box-folder 107)
      - American Interests, Gorbachev's Soviet Economic Institute, undated (Box-folder 107)
      - American Interests, 1982 January 19 (Box-folder 108)
      - American Interests, "Should former U.S. officials represent foreign interests?" 2 cassettes, 1986 March 29 (Box-folder 108)
      - American Interests, Reagan foreign policy legacy, 1987 September (Box-folder 108)
      - American Interests, FSX deal with Japan, 1989 February 14 (Box-folder 108)
      - American Interests, Follow the money, 1989 July 12 (Box-folder 108)
      - American Interests, Korea, 1989 October 14 (Box-folder 108)
      - American Interests, "Are foreign agents sabotaging America's economy?", 1990 October 6 (Box-folder 108)
      - American Interests, Korea and U.S. trade, 1991 April 25 (Box-folder 108)
      - ANB TV Asahi, Post Brezhnev, 1982 November 11 (Box-folder 108)
      - Antenna in Washington with Despina Skenders, 1991 October 13 (Box-folder 108)
      - BBC Newsnight, U.S./Japan, 1989 April 17 (Box-folder 108)
      - BBC Newsnight, Richard Allen interview, 1991 February 28 (Box-folder 108)
      - BBC Vatican, 1997 September 11 (Box-folder 109)
      - Capitol Edition, Jamestown Foundation, 1988 June 26 (Box-folder 109)
      - Capitol Watch, Representative Billy Tauzin and Dick Allen, 1994 November 30 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBC Journal, Korean airliner, 1983 September 22 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBN News, Japanese investments in U.S., 1989 February 17 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBN News, President Clinton's foreign policy, 1993 October 6 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBN 700 Club, Summit meeting, 1985 November 15 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBN 700 Club, 1988 July 12 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBS Face the Nation, 2 cassettes, 1986 June 1 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBS Nightwatch, Political situation in South Korea, 1987 April 21 (Box-folder 109)
      - CBS Nightwatch, Pat Choate and Richard Allen regarding book Agents of Influence, 1990 October 3 (Box-folder 109)
      - CNN unaired story on "revolving door," undated (Box-folder 109)
      - CNN Pre and Post Debate shows, 1984 October 21 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Newsmaker Saturday on arms control, 1986 October 25 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Richard Allen and Bernard Shaw Korea, 1988 October 18 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN International News Hour on situation in Poland, 1989 August 17 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN International News Hour on United Nations, 1991 September (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN special on Vince Foster suicide, 1993 August 16 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Novak interview with Kim Young Sam, 1993 September 11 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Business Asia, 1994 July 7 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Business Asia, 1995 January 5 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Capital Gang, 1989 November 25 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Capital Gang, 1990 August 4 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Capital Gang, 1991 February 16 (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Crossfire 15th Anniversary, undated (Box-folder 110)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1982 July (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1986 November 10 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1987 January 21 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1987 January 21 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 2 cassettes, 1987 June 15 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1987 September 22 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1987 November 25 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1989 February 24 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1989 May 8 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1989 May 22 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1990 August 9 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1990 November 2 (Box-folder 111)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1990 November 2 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1991 January 8 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1991 April 4 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1991 April 16 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Crossfire, 2 cassettes, 1992 January 16 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1993 December 28 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Crossfire, 1997 March 10 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1987 April 7 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1987 July 20 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1989 February 15 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1990 January 4 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1991 February 11 (Box-folder 112)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1991 February 20 (Box-folder 113)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1991 April 15 (Box-folder 113)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1991 April 15-16 (Box-folder 113)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1992 August 27 (Box-folder 113)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1992 October 21 (Box-folder 113)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1993 August 11 (Box-folder 113)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1994 June 10 (Box-folder 113)
      - CSPAN Paula Stern Debate, "International diplomats of Washington,", 1992 October 22 (Box-folder 113)
      - CSPAN Live viewer call in regarding events in Moscow, 1993 October 4 (Box-folder 113)
      - CSPAN2 Senator Kit Bonds on North Korea, 1993 November 22 (Box-folder 113)
      - CSPAN2 "Presidential toasts,", 1993 November 23 (Box-folder 113)
      - Democratic ethics spot, network news coverage, 1984 March 28 (Box-folder 113)
      - FNN Focus, Japanese influence politics, 1990 October 4 (Box-folder 113)
      - Fox, City under siege with Don Allison, 1990 January 4 (Box-folder 114)
      - Fox Cable News, Reagan presidency, 1998 May 5 (Box-folder 114)
      - Inside Washington, 2 cassettes, 1992 (Box-folder 114)
      - Japanese network coverage of Richard V. Allen leaving the White House, 1982 January (Box-folder 114)
      - Jesse Jackson show, undated (Box-folder 114)
      - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour, AWACS, 1981 September (Box-folder 114)
      - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour, 1986 November 24 (Box-folder 114)
      - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour, 1987 (Box-folder 114)
      - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour, 1991 June 13 (Box-folder 114)
      - NBC Dateline, Holy alliance: Ronald Reagan and the Pope, 2 cassettes, 1996 September 22 (Box-folder 114)
      - NBC Meet the Press, 2 cassettes, 1980 October (Box-folder 114)
      - NBC Meet the Press, 1980 November (Box-folder 115)
      - NBC Nightly News, 1988 February 19 (Box-folder 115)
      - NBC Today Show, 1986 August 12 (Box-folder 115)
      - NBC Today Show, 1986 November 17 (Box-folder 115)
      - NBC Today Show, 1986 November 26 (Box-folder 115)
      - Panorama: slander, 1984 December 12 (Box-folder 115)
      - Paula Dobriensky, "Global dateline: foreign policy challenges,", 1994 October 26 (Box-folder 115)
      - Paula Dobriensky, "Freedom's challenge,", 1996 July 25 (Box-folder 115)
      - Paula Dobriensky, "Worldwise,", 1997 May 7 (Box-folder 115)
      - Planet Hollywood Seoul opening, 1994 May 27 (Box-folder 116)
      - This is America with Dennis Wholey, 6 cassettes, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 116)
      - UPI The Insiders, 2 cassettes, 1990 March (Box-folder 116)
    - Iran Contra/October Surprise, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 117-118)
      - NBC Iran/Iraq special report, 1982 (Box-folder 117)
      - President Reagan's address on Iran, 1986 November 13 (Box-folder 117)
      - NBC special report: Iran/NSC role, 1986 November 25 (Box-folder 117)
      - Oliver North testimony before congressional committee, 5 cassettes, 1986 July 6-9 (Box-folder 117)
      - Blank, undated (Box-folder 117)
      - Panorama, "Private Wars of Colonel North,", 1987 March 15 (Box-folder 117)
      - Oliver North, 1987 July 14 (Box-folder 117)
      - Nightline, Gary Sick allegations, 1991 April 15 (Box-folder 117)
      - Frontline, Reagan campaign and release of hostages from Iran, 1991 April 16 (Box-folder 117)
      - Good Morning America, Richard V. Allen and David Aaron re: Gary Sick, 2 cassettes, 1991 April 16 (Box-folder 118)
      - CBS Nightwatch, Richard V. Allen with Gary Sick "Hostagegate,", 1991 April 23 (Box-folder 118)
      - Monitor TV, Possible investigation into Sick allegations, 1991 May 2 (Box-folder 118)
      - The Today Show, Richard V. Allen with Gary Sick, 1991 May 2 (Box-folder 118)
      - Fox Morning News, Richard Allen interview, 1991 May 2 (Box-folder 118)
      - October surprise package, Mike McKee reporter/CONUS communications, 1991 May 3 (Box-folder 118)
      - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour, Richard V. Allen and Gary Sick, 1991 May 3 (Box-folder 118)
      - Nightline, Discussion of October Surprise and hostage deal, 1991 June 20 (Box-folder 118)
      - Face the Nation, with Congressman Lee Hamilton, Gary Sick, Ed Meese, 1991 July 7 (Box-folder 118)
      - Nightline, with Gary Sick, Jeff Greenfield, Steve Emerson, 1991 November 12 (Box-folder 118)
      - CBC Journal, October Surprise, 1991 November 25 (Box-folder 118)
      - Crossfire, "Free at Last,", 1991 December 4 (Box-folder 118)
    - Sporting Events, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 118)
      - Special Olympics, undated (Box-folder 119)
      - The World to Seoul, undated (Box-folder 119)
      - Seoul Olympic videotape, 1985 January 13 (Box-folder 119)
      - 10th Asian Games, Venues and Support Facilities, 1986 (Box-folder 119)
      - Opening ceremony of the 10th Asian Games, 1986 (Box-folder 119)
      - Closing ceremony of the 10th Asian Games, 1986 (Box-folder 119)
      - Seoul, 1988 (Box-folder 119)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 119)
      - American Environmental Review, 1998 (Box-folder 119)
      - Catholic Campaign for America convention, 1995 November 17-18 (Box-folder 119)
      - Communism is Dead... Now What?, 2 cassettes, 1992 June 6 (Box-folder 119)
      - The Great Debate, Notre Dame Class of 1957, 2 cassettes, undated (Box-folder 119)
      - Great Decisions, 13 cassettes, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 120)
      - Great Decisions, 5 cassettes, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 121)
      - Heritage Foundation visit to Asia, 2 cassettes, 1986 (Box-folder 121)
      - Heritage 10 Banquet with President Reagan, 1986 April 22 (Box-folder 121)
      - Heritage Foundation seminar on US-ROK relations, 1989 October 10 (Box-folder 121)
      - Heritage Foundation Asian studies conference "The U.S. Response to Possible North Korean Aggression," 2 cassettes, 1993 December 15 (Box-folder 121)
      - Heritage Foundation B.C. Lee lecture with the Honorable Henry Kissinger, 1995 February 1 (Box-folder 121)
      - Heritage Foundation President's Club meeting, 1996 December 3 (Box-folder 121)
      - Heritage Foundation President's Club meeting, 1996 December 3 (Box-folder 122)
      - House Foreign Affairs Committee, Korea update, 1986 April 16 (Box-folder 122)
      - House Rules Committee, China technology transfer investigation, 1998 June 16 (Box-folder 122)
      - Hypotheticals, War and Peace, 2 cassettes, 1991 September 13 (Box-folder 122)
      - IDU: Bush/Thatcher speeches, 1985 July 25 (Box-folder 122)
      - IDU convention, 2 cassettes, 1996 (Box-folder 122)
      - Inside Washington, 5 cassettes, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 122)
      - Inside Washington, 1993 (Box-folder 123)
      - New Media Bible, 4 cassettes, 1979 (Box-folder 123)
      - President's Cup, 2 cassettes, 1994 (Box-folder 123)
      - Rough Riders, 1997 (Box-folder 123)
      - Richard V. Allen composites 3 and 4, 1981 November 28 (Box-folder 123)
      - Satellite special: "A Close Look at U.S. Japan Relations," 2 cassettes, 1988 (Box-folder 124)
      - State of the Union, 1987 May 3 (Box-folder 124)
      - Strauss, undated. In German (Box-folder 124)
      - Sugihara, 1994 September 19 (Box-folder 124)
      - Taejon congressional video, undated (Box-folder 124)
      - Tuesday Team, "The Reagan Presidency,", 1984 September 12 (Box-folder 124)
      - Vpielgrzymka Papieża do Polski, 1997 (Box-folder 124)
    - Large format studio tapes, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 124)
      - Richard V. Allen on Meet the Press, 2 cassettes, 1980 October 19 (Box-folder 125)
      - ABC Issues and Answers, 1980 December 5 (Box-folder 125)
      - Nightline, Resignation of Richard V. Allen, 1982 January 4 (Box-folder 125)
      - American Interests, Brzezinski/Allen, 1982 January 18 (Box-folder 125)
      - CNN Freeman Reports, "From the Outside Looking In,", 1982 January 27 (Box-folder 125)
      - Richard Allen Composite, tapes 1-4, 1982 January (Box-folder 126)
      - Richard Allen Composite, tapes 5-6, 1982 January (Box-folder 127)
      - Legacy of Greatness, Republican National Committee, 1982 January (Box-folder 127)
      - CNN Crossfire, 2 cassettes, 1982 July 8 (Box-folder 127)
      - ABC Nightline, 1983 March 4 (Box-folder 128)
      - CBC Journal, 1983 April 27 (Box-folder 128)
      - ITN Channel Four News, 1983 August 12 (Box-folder 128)
      - CNN Pre-Debate Show, 1984 October 21 (Box-folder 128)
      - CNN Post-Debate Show, 1984 October 21 (Box-folder 128)
      - Armburst NSTC 525, 1986 February (Box-folder 128)
      - CNN Larry King Live, 1986 November 19 (Box-folder 129)
      - Morning News: Hill - Allen and Rollins, 1986 December 3 (Box-folder 129)
    - Beta format, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 129)
      - Satellite special, "A close look at U.S. Japan relations," undated (Box-folder 130)
      - Richard V. Allen's honorary degree in Seoul, undated (Box-folder 130)
      - Tokyo broadcast, undated (Box-folder 130)
      - ABC Viewpoint, 1982 August 12 (Box-folder 130)
      - MBC-TV Seoul, "World '85,", 1985 January 1 (Box-folder 130)
      - CBC U.S./U.S.S.R. summit, 1985 October 29 (Box-folder 130)
      - Tribune broadcasting, Gary Sick saga, 1991 May 1 (Box-folder 130)
    - Other Formats, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 131-132)
      - CBN, Public Ethics with Jodi Hasset, 1986 May 30 (Box-folder 131)
      - NBC Today, 1986 November 17 (Box-folder 131)
      - NBC Nightly News, 1986 December 19 (Box-folder 131)
      - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour, 1987 May 13 (Box-folder 131)
      - CNN, Olympics, 2 cassettes, 1987 August 6 (Box-folder 131)
      - TV Tokyo, Channel 12, Ichiro Murata, "Reagan Legacy,", 1989 January 20 (Box-folder 132)
      - China TV, Story of CIB and Richard V. Allen regarding President Bush's visit to People's Republic of China, 1979 February 15 (Box-folder 132)
      - THF State visit, 2 8mm cassettes, undated (Box-folder 132)
      - CNN Business Day, 1992 March 3 (Box-folder 132)